# Jeremy Stegall

## GDOT CEI |Junior Web Developer

Atlanta, GA | (678)-602-0078 jeremy.stegall77@gmail.com

Currently a GDOT project manager and construction inspector for Atlas Technical Consultants, Jeremy has 7+ years experience working on CID projects in Gwinnett County, and also spent 20 years in the service industry. He is a 2020 graduate from Digital Crafts Software Development Boot camp, focusing on full-stack web development and design. He is a strong and dedicated employee with marked communicative, interpersonal, team working and leadership skills, having a constant drive to gain new skills and knowledge. Not afraid to face diverse challenges, Jeremy is an asset to current and future employers.

## Professional Skills/Certifications

- OSHA 10, Current
- SWCC, Current
- WECS, Current
- Field Concrete Technician Certification, Current
- Web Design & Development
  - > HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React
  - https://jeremy-stegall.herokuapp.com/
  - ➤ https://github.com/JRStegall
- MS Office, Excel, PowerPoint
- Music Composition & Arrangement

### Education

## DigitalCrafts | Certificate in Software Engineering |Atlanta, GA

June 2020-December 2020

- Software engineering training program covering full-stack development including, but not limited to: Debugging, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, REACT, RESTfulAPI, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL and Sequelize
- Worked in team settings simulating real world experience to build projects based upon the languages and concepts being taught, highlighting the individual strengths of team members.

## **Work Experience**

## Atlas Technical Consultants | Atlanta, GA May 2017 - Present

- Construction Inspector and Project Manager for GDOT projects in Gwinnett County, overseeing multiple facets of road construction and maintenance including, but not limited to: CID projects, resurfacing, storm drain installation, water main installation, sewer force main installation, utilities relocation, bridge inspection
- Daily communications with contractor and supervisor to insure all work being done is up to GDOT standards
- Responsible for monthly payment statements based upon work completed
- Responsible for insuring that the materials and techniques used by contractors are compliant with GDOT standards and details

#### Kueffer Cranes, INC. | Atlanta, GA

October 2013 – September 2015

Warehouse manager responsible for daily operations of warehouse:

- Shipping and receiving
- Parts ordering and delivery
- Daily communications with techs to insure they have parts and materials needed to complete a job

### Service Industry | Indianapolis, IN/Atlanta, GA

1995-2015

- ♦ BOH: Dishwasher, Prep Cook, Line Cook, Shift Leader, Crew Leader, AKM, KM
- FOH: Bar Back, Bartender, MIT (manager in training)